artbeats.com 2005-04-04

# Artbeats - Privacy Policy

**Philosophy**  
Artbeats is committed to protecting our users' privacy. This statement is meant to inform our users of how we define, gather and utilize personally identifiable information. Artbeats will take reasonable steps to protect user privacy consistent within the guidelines set forth in this policy and the law. 

**Personal Information**  
We ask you for your address, telephone number, e-mail address and other personal information during the registration process. This information is primarily used for our own purposes; however, we reserve the right to share our customer lists with approved companies. This means that you may receive marketing materials from companies that have products you may be interested in. If you request during your registration that we do not share your information, it will not be shared. **Your e-mail address will not be shared with other companies in any event** ; however, Artbeats may use e-mail to send you information from us and possibly other companies', including special offers, newsletters, and press releases.You can request to "opt-out" of these e-mail newsletters at any time by following the instructions in the e-mail message. 

**Transaction Information**  
When you order from our site, we ask you to complete an order form that requests certain information from you including financial information such as a credit card number and expiration date and general contact details. We use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e. to deliver information, products or other services that you order and to invoice you. We do not store your credit card information, but we do store your mailing and shipping addresses and other contact information. 

**Cookies**  
As a standard practice, Artbeats assigns a unique number to each user for anonymously tracking content preferences and traffic patterns. This number is kept in a file on your computer called a "cookie." This allows you to automatically log-in to our site and it allows us to track how visitors use our site, without us really knowing who those visitors are. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there, and what items visitors are searching for. We use all this information in order to improve our content, plan future products and measure overall site effectiveness. 

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (However, by not accepting cookies, some of our web pages may not display properly or you may not be able to access certain pages.) 

Sharing Information Artbeats discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 25% of our users are interested in Sports footage, etc) in order to describe our services to prospective partners and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. We don't tell other companies specific information about any of our users. 

**Password**  
Your Artbeats User Account Information is password-protected in order to secure your personal information. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Artbeats employees will never ask for passwords in unsolicited phone calls or unsolicited e-mails. Remember to close your browser window and clear your history when you have finished to ensure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a computer with someone else, or if you are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe. 

**Legal Requirments**  
Artbeats may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law. 

Artbeats may modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time. 

If you have any queries about this policy please feel free to contact our webmaster at: [webmaster@artbeats.com](mailto:webmaster@artbeats.com)
